# Minh Nguyen

## Graphic Designer / Marketing Coordinator

Phone: (512) 825 9661

Email: MinhStudios@gmail.com
Portfolio: www.Minhstudios.com
Linkedin.com/in/minhstudios

## **Summary**

A graphic designer with eight years of professional experience focused on print, illustration, logo, and web design. Minh also has experience with WordPress, branding, photography, marketing, and visual arts. He aims to have continued advancement in web development as part of his goal set. After getting his BFA at Texas State University and completing an internship in San Antonio (Clockwork Studios), Minh began working in-house for a real estate firm where he was immersed in website design, real estate photography, print, and direct mail. After some contract work, he soon became a marketing coordinator for Newmark Knight Frank and works with reputable clients to market their commercial real estate assets.

# **Experience**

### MARKETING COORDINATOR | DEC 2017 - SEPT 2020 Newmark Knight Frank, Austin, TX

- » Marketed over +\$1 billion in multifamily real estate transactions
- » Coordinate on-time schedules with clients and hired photographers
- » Production of high quality fliers, proposals and offering memorandums
- » Created property listing websites with Listing Lab interface
- » Video editing for property listings and website uploading
- » Extensive market research for the Central Texas office, national Manufacturing Housing group, and national Student Housing group
- » Schedule and executing website launches and email campaigns per listing
- \* Created a database of photographer list for marketing department
- \* Integrated new email marketing campaign process for marketing department

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER | NOV 2017 - May 2018 (Contractor) Texas Hospital Association, Austin, TX

- » Produced white pages from given context using THA branding
- » Created additional logo designs for following company branding
- » Communicate with team on "Basecamp" workflow tool

## GRAPHIC+WEB DESIGNER / PHOTOGRAPHER | NOV 2014 - NOV 2017 The Carvajal Group, Austin, TX

- Designed fliers, brochures, banners, direct mail, logos, and print materials
- » Produced MLS signs, billboard graphics, and magazine ads
- » Created and maintain WordPress website for per property listing
- » Drove to property listings to take exterior and interior photos
- » Post edit and finalize real estate photos for print and media
- » Direct mail campaign to specific strategized market region
- » Daily email blast campaign to specific clients and investors
- Provided real estate photography inhouse to reduce marketing cost
- \* Created branding for a new broker group used on social media
- \* Reduced print service costs by 33% through negotiations

#### INTERN GRAPHIC DESIGNER | JAN 2012 - MAY 2012 Clockwork Studios, San Antonio, TX

- » Working on editorials, newsletters, and brochures
- » Created original logos for personal portfolio
- » Idea contribution & Poster design for clients in Seattle / San Antonio
- » Assist senior designers on design material and content
- \* One of the pitched ideas to client was in final selection

## **Education**

COMMUNICATION DESIGN | 2006 - 2010 BFA | Texas State University | San Marcos, TX Cum Laude Achievement | GPA: 3.7

#### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

» Dean's List 2009 & 2010

#### **RELEVANT COURSES**

- » Communication Design
- » Web Design
- » Illustration & Drawing
- » Trademark Design
- » Art Direction
- » Typography I & II
- » Photography
- » Art History
- Web Design
- » Sculpture & Painting

# **Skill Set / Abilities**

**Design Software**: Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Dreamweaver, Flash, and Premiere

#### Web-Based Application:

HTML/CSS, FTP Client and WordPress

Hand Skills: Drawing, Painting, and Printmaking

## Office Applications:

MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Office 365, Mac, PC

#### Photography:

Real Estate Photography and Lightroom post editing

#### Campaign E-Blast Interface:

Listing Lab, CampaignBreeze, RealtyJuggler